No bib. No crib. No problem.
Baby's Day Out is a comedy, adventure, family film
directed by Patrick Read Johnson.
Baby Bink couldn't ask for more: he has adoring (if somewhat sickly-sweet) parents, lives in a
huge mansion, and he's just about to appear in the social pages of the paper.
Unfortunately, not everyone in the world is as nice as Baby Bink's parents—especially the
three enterprising kidnappers who pretend to be photographers from the newspaper.
Successfully kidnapping Baby Bink, they have a harder time keeping hold of the rascal, who not only keeps one step
ahead of them, but seems to be more than a little bit smarter than the three bumbling criminals.
Eddie, played by Joe Mantegna.
Laraine, played by Lara Flynn Boyle.
Norby, played by Joe Pantoliano.
Veeko, played by Brian Haley.
Gilbertine, played by Cynthia Nixon.
FBI Agent Grissom, played by Fred Thompson.
Baby's Day Out is a 1994 American adventure comedy film directed by Patrick Read Johnson
and written by John Hughes, who also served as producer with Richard Vane.
Starring Joe Mantegna, Lara Flynn Boyle, Joe Pantoliano, and Brian Haley, the film centers on a wealthy baby's abduction by
three criminals, his subsequent escape and adventure through Chicago while being pursued by the criminals.
Released on July 1, 1994, by 20th Century Fox in the United States, the film was a
box-office bomb, grossing only $30 million against a $48 million budget.
Despite being panned by critics, it has since gained a cult following.
Baby's Day Out was a commercial success in India.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois,
baby, kidnapping, gorilla, stupidity.
The tone is lighthearted.